<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
	<maintainer type="person"><email>maintainer-wanted@gentoo.org</email></maintainer>
	<use>
		<flag name='abakan'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Abakan</flag>
		<flag name='almetevsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Almetevsk</flag>
		<flag name='arkhangelsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Arkhangelsk</flag>
		<flag name='armawir'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Armawir</flag>
		<flag name='astrakhan'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Astrakhan</flag>
		<flag name='barnaul'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Barnaul</flag>
		<flag name='belgorod'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Belgorod</flag>
		<flag name='biysk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Biysk</flag>
		<flag name='blagoveshensk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Blagoveshensk</flag>
		<flag name='bratsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Bratsk</flag>
		<flag name='bryansk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Bryansk</flag>
		<flag name='v_novgorod'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for V_Novgorod</flag>
		<flag name='vladivostok'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Vladivostok</flag>
		<flag name='vladimir'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Vladimir</flag>
		<flag name='volgograd'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Volgograd</flag>
		<flag name='vologda'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Vologda</flag>
		<flag name='voronezh'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Voronezh</flag>
		<flag name='gornoaltaysk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Gornoaltaysk</flag>
		<flag name='ekaterinburg'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ekaterinburg</flag>
		<flag name='ivanovo'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ivanovo</flag>
		<flag name='izhevsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Izhevsk</flag>
		<flag name='irkutsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Irkutsk</flag>
		<flag name='yoshkarola'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Yoshkarola</flag>
		<flag name='kazan'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kazan</flag>
		<flag name='kaliningrad'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kaliningrad</flag>
		<flag name='kaluga'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kaluga</flag>
		<flag name='kemerovo'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kemerovo</flag>
		<flag name='kirov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kirov</flag>
		<flag name='komsomolsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Komsomolsk</flag>
		<flag name='kostroma'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kostroma</flag>
		<flag name='krasnodar'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Krasnodar</flag>
		<flag name='krasnoyarsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Krasnoyarsk</flag>
		<flag name='kurgan'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kurgan</flag>
		<flag name='kursk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kursk</flag>
		<flag name='lenkuz'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Lenkuz</flag>
		<flag name='lipetsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Lipetsk</flag>
		<flag name='magnitogorsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Magnitogorsk</flag>
		<flag name='miass'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Miass</flag>
		<flag name='moscow'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Moscow</flag>
		<flag name='murmansk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Murmansk</flag>
		<flag name='nabchelny'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Nabchelny</flag>
		<flag name='nahodka'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Nahodka</flag>
		<flag name='nizhnevartovsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Nizhnevartovsk</flag>
		<flag name='n_novgorod'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for N_Novgorod</flag>
		<flag name='ntagil'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ntagil</flag>
		<flag name='novokuznetsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Novokuznetsk</flag>
		<flag name='novorossiysk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Novorossiysk</flag>
		<flag name='novosibirsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Novosibirsk</flag>
		<flag name='norilsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Norilsk</flag>
		<flag name='noyabrsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Noyabrsk</flag>
		<flag name='omsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Omsk</flag>
		<flag name='orel'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Orel</flag>
		<flag name='orenburg'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Orenburg</flag>
		<flag name='penza'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Penza</flag>
		<flag name='perm'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Perm</flag>
		<flag name='petrozavodsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Petrozavodsk</flag>
		<flag name='p_kamchatskiy'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for P_kamchatskiy</flag>
		<flag name='pskov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Pskov</flag>
		<flag name='minvody'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Minvody</flag>
		<flag name='rostov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Rostov</flag>
		<flag name='ryazan'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ryazan</flag>
		<flag name='samara'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Samara</flag>
		<flag name='spb'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Spb</flag>
		<flag name='saransk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Saransk</flag>
		<flag name='saratov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Saratov</flag>
		<flag name='smolensk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Smolensk</flag>
		<flag name='sochi'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Sochi</flag>
		<flag name='stavropol'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Stavropol</flag>
		<flag name='staroskol'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Staroskol</flag>
		<flag name='sterlitamak'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Sterlitamak</flag>
		<flag name='surgut'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Surgut</flag>
		<flag name='syktyvkar'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Syktyvkar</flag>
		<flag name='tambov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tambov</flag>
		<flag name='tver'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tver</flag>
		<flag name='tobolsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tobolsk</flag>
		<flag name='togliatti'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Togliatti</flag>
		<flag name='tomsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tomsk</flag>
		<flag name='tula'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tula</flag>
		<flag name='tyumen'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Tyumen</flag>
		<flag name='ulanude'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ulanude</flag>
		<flag name='ulyanovsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ulyanovsk</flag>
		<flag name='ussuriysk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ussuriysk</flag>
		<flag name='ufa'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ufa</flag>
		<flag name='khabarovsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Khabarovsk</flag>
		<flag name='cheboksary'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Cheboksary</flag>
		<flag name='chelyabinsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Chelyabinsk</flag>
		<flag name='chita'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Chita</flag>
		<flag name='yuzhnosakhalinsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Yuzhnosakhalinsk</flag>
		<flag name='yakutsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Yakutsk</flag>
		<flag name='yaroslavl'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Yaroslavl</flag>
		<flag name='donetsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Donetsk</flag>
		<flag name='odessa'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Odessa</flag>
		<flag name='dnepropetrovsk'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Dnepropetrovsk</flag>
		<flag name='almaty'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Almaty</flag>
		<flag name='karaganda'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Karaganda</flag>
		<flag name='ustkam'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Ustkam</flag>
		<flag name='limassol'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Limassol</flag>
		<flag name='nicosia'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Nicosia</flag>
		<flag name='praha'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Praha</flag>
		<flag name='padova'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Padova</flag>
		<flag name='santiago'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Santiago</flag>
		<flag name='dubai'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Dubai</flag>
		<flag name='k_uralskiy'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for K_uralskiy</flag>
		<flag name='kharkov'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Kharkov</flag>
		<flag name='astana'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Astana</flag>
		<flag name='pavlodar'>Install GeoInformational data (incl. maps) for Pavlodar</flag>
	</use>
</pkgmetadata>
